A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office and Home Files FA1353
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal Papers and Interests, 1888-2010; 1; 118.83 Cubic Feet 281 containers.
  - Mary French Rockefeller and Family Files, 1888-2008; 1_2
    - MFR - YWCA - Elizabeth Arden, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 374, Folder 5)
    - MFR - YWCA, 1955-1996 (Box 374, Folder 6)
    - MFR - Memorial Service for Elizabeth French Hitchcock, 1976 (Box 374, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Correspondence - Charles Sayward, 1960-1997 (Box 374, Folder 8)
    - MFR - Bobst Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Republican Closed Circuit Dinner, 1960; 1964 (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Publications - Miscellaneous, 1956-2002 (Box 375, Folder 3-4)
    - MFR - YWCA Files, 1990s (Box 375, Folder 5-6, Box 376, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Appeals - Firestone, 1963-1985 (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Appeals - General Electric, 1963-1966 (Box 376, Folder 3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Appeals - National Board, 1973-1989 (Box 376, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - Centennial Scrapbook, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - LSR - YWCA - Retirement Fund Scrapbook, 2002 (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - LSR - New York State Senate Resolution - Tribute to MFR, 1997 (Box 376, Folder 7)
    - MFR - Gift List (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Blue Hill Troupe Librettos, c. 1930s (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Art Books (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children (AACC) - Reports, 1940s (Box 377, Folder 5-6)
    - LSR - Correspondence with Parents, 1943-1944 (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - MFR - Children's Village - Giving, 1920s-1940s (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Clothing, 1998 (Box 393, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Memorial - Programs, 1997 (Box 393, Folder 3)
    - ACMNP - Tribute to MFR, 1997 (Box 393, Folder 4)
    - MFR - MSKCC - Art Committee, 1975-2000 (Box 393, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Memorial - Gifts, 1997 (Box 393, Folder 6)
    - MFR - Larry Rockefeller - Memorial Service Remarks, 1997 (Box 393, Folder 7)
    - MFR - YWCA - Contribution Lists, 1997 (Box 394, Folder 1)
    - John Bowling Associates - MFR Memorial Service, 1997 (Box 394, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Memorial Gifts, 1997 (Box 394, Folder 3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Contributions in Memory of MFR, 1997 (Box 394, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1994 (Box 394, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Contributions 1996 - A-L (Box 394, Folder 6)
    - Choate Rosemary Hall - MFR Tribute, 1997 (Box 394, Folder 7)
    - MFR - ACMNP, 1991 (Box 394, Folder 8)
    - MFR - ACMNP, 1992-1996 (Box 395, Folder 1)
    - LSR - A Christmas Message, 1997 (Box 395, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel, 1950s (Box 395, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Travel - Hawaii - Photos - Candid, 1968 (Box 395, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Guides, 1950s-1980s (Box 395, Folder 5, Box 396, Folder 1-4, Box 397, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Diaries, 1940s-1980s (Box 397, Folder 3, Box 398, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - EWHA University Foundation - 90th Anniversary Award, 1976 (Box 398, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Diaries, 1930s-1990s (Box 398, Folder 4, Box 400, Folder 1-3)
    - LSR - Appraisals - LSR and AAR Collections, 1948-1978 (Box 399, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Pins and Awards, 1950s-1990s (Box 399, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Diaries, 1960s (Box 399, Folder 3)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Address Books (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Miscellaneous, 1920s-1990s (Box 401, Folder 2-4, Box 402, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Bible Year Book, 1921 January (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary M. Billings French from her mother M. S. Billings, 1888-1904 (Box 402, Folder 3)
      Mary M. Billings French is MFR's mother. M. S. Billings is MFR's grandmother.
    - MFR - Notebooks/Day Books - Mary M. Billings French, 1922-1945 (Box 402, Folder 4, Box 403, Folder 1-2)
      Mary M. Billings French is MFR's mother.
    - MFR - Billings and French Families - Genealogies, 1992-1994 (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - MFR - Memorial Tributes, 1997 (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - MFR - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French - Memorial Service, 1976 (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - LSR-MFR - Wedding Photo, 1934 August 15 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Memorabilia, 1977 (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Brooke Astor (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - LSR-MFR - Lyndon B. Johnson, 1964-1973 (Box 404, Folder 8)
    - MFR - Winston Churchill Memorial Library, 2001 (Box 404, Folder 9)
    - LSR-MFR - Miscellaneous Memorabilia (Box 404, Folder 10)
    - LSR - National Urban League - A Family Exhibit Brochure, 1959 (Box 412, Folder 6)
  - LSR Family and Rockefeller Family Member Files, 1924-2009; 1_3
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Family, 2003-2004 (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Stepchildren, 2003-2004 (Box 379, Folder 1)
      Carol Lyden; Anne Bartley (WR's stepdaughter)
      Restricted - Open in 2042
    - LSR - Rockefeller, David Sr., 2003-2004 (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Adam Growald (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - LSR - David and Diana Rockefeller, 2003-2004 (Box 379, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Peggy Dulany (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - LSR - French Family, 2000-2004 (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Larry French, 1995-2004 (Box 379, Folder 6, Box 380, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Waletzky, Jacob - Condolence Letters, 2001 (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Waletzky, Jacob - Funeral, 2001-2002 (Box 378, Folder 5)
      Memorial Service; mass cards, sympathy letters, correspondence.
    - LSR - Waletzky, Jacob, 2000s (Box 378, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Jay and Sharon, 2000-2004 (Box 378, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Hope Aldrich, 2000-2004 (Box 378, Folder 8)
    - LSR - LSR Art - NAR Estate, 1990s-2004 (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler (Happy), 1990s-2004 (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Mark and Renee, 1990s-2004 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Rodman and Sascha, 1990s-2004 (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Roberts, Ann Rockefeller, 1990s-2004 (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Steven C., 1990s-2004 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Jr., 1990s-2004 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Miscellaneous, 1990s-2004 (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family Tree, 2002 (Box 381, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family Weekend, 2004 June (Box 381, Folder 7)
    - LSR - O'Neill, Abby and George - Family, 1990s-2004 (Box 381, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Dulany, Peggy R., 1990s-2005 (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Goodwin, Neva R., 1990s-2005 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Growald, Adam, 1990s-2005 (Box 380, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Growald, Eileen R., 1990s-2005 (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Growald, Paul - Coevolution Institute, 1990s-2005 (Box 380, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, David - Correspondence, 1988-2004 (Box 382, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, David - Stone Barns, 1990s-2005 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, David - Autobiography "Memoirs", 1990s-2004 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, David - White House Photographs, 1998 February 19 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, David - Periodicals, 1998-2002 (Box 382, Folder 6)
      Vanity Fair and Art and Antique. Both feature David Rockefeller.
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Diana N., 1990s-2005 (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Peggy McGrath, 1996 March (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, David, Jr. (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Senator John D., IV, and Family, 1990s-2005 (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd, 1990s-2005 (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Dedication of JDR Memorial Window, Union Church, 1965 October 10 (Box 384, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Christian Church (Box 384, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Martha Baird (Box 384, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, John D., Sr. (Box 384, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 384, Folder 7, Box 385, Folder 1-2, Box 386, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Memorial Service, 1979 February 2 (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Mary T. Clark (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Margaretta F. (Happy), 1990s-2004 (Box 386, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Mark F. and Renee Anisto, 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Meile L., 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Michael S. and Tara Scully, 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Jr., 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Peter C. and Allison, 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Richard, 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Rodman C. and Sascha M., 1990s-2004 (Box 386, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Sharon Percy, 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Steven, Jr., 1990s-2004 (Box 383, Folder 10)
      Restricted - Open in 2024
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Steven, Sr. Family, 1965-2004 (Box 387, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Steven, Sr. - Correspondence, 1988-2004 (Box 387, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Steven, Sr. - Publications (Box 386, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1965-2004 (Box 386, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul, 1965-2004 (Box 386, Folder 7)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry - General Correspondence (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry - LR Speech - Scenic Hudson Gala, 1994 June 1 (Box 386, Folder 8)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry - LR Testimony, 1993 October 6 (Box 386, Folder 9)
      Before Assembly and Senate Committees on Tourism, Recreation, Environment.
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry - LR Campaign Announcement and Background, 1991-1992 (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry - Beaverkill, 1994-1995 (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry, 1960s (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Larry, 1970s-1980s (Box 415, Folder 1-3)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Wyatt Gordon, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 1)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Rockefeller, Ryan Laurance, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 2)
    - LSR Family - Chasin, Laura R., 1990s-2004 (Box 388, Folder 3)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Chasin, Laura R. - Public Conversations Project, 1990-2003 (Box 388, Folder 4-6)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Chasin, Laura R. - "Alphabet of MFR" Book, 1997 (Box 390, Folder 2)
      Compiled by Laura Chasin in memory of her mother.
    - LSR - LSR Family - Chasin, Laura, 1950s-1980s (Box 413, Folder 2-4)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Case, Peter Rockefeller, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 3)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Case, Matthew Owen, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 4)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Wagner, Jessica Case, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Waletzky, Lucy, 1950s-1980s (Box 414, Folder 1-2)
      Restricted - LSR estate - Open in 2029
    - LSR - LSR Family - Case, James, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 6)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Weber, Marion R., 1996 (Box 389, Folder 7)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Basilio, Tony, 1989-1993 (Box 413, Folder 5)
      Tony Basilio was a friend of Marion Weber.
    - LSR - LSR Family - Weber, Marion, 1950s-1980s (Box 414, Folder 3-4)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Ortiz, Rachel French Weber and Alexandro, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 8)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Weinstein, Elizabeth Parmly Weber, 1990s-2004 (Box 389, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - LSR - NAR Institute (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - LSR - NAR Rabbit Club, 1979, 1999 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - LSR - NAR Campaign Pins, 1950s-1960s (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Correspondence - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1924 (Box 404, Folder 7)
  - Financial Reviews, 1988-2004; 1_4
    - LSR - Financial Reviews, 1988-1991, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Insurance - General, 1994-2004 (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Annual Financial Reviews, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - LSR Fund, 1988-2007; 1_5
    - LSR Fund - Eagle Properties, Inc. - Nalibow House to LSR Fund, 1999-2001 (Box 33, Folder 10, Box 34, Folder 1)
    - LSR Fund - Creation, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - LSR Fund - Jean Houston Film Project, 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - LSR Fund - Financial Reports, 1995-2000 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - LSR Fund - Maui Property - Sale to Conservation Fund - General, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - LSR Fund - Maui Property - Sale to Conservation Fund - Warranty, Deed, Contract, Title Report (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
    - LSR Fund - Moyers, Bill (PBS) - General, 1998-2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - LSR Fund - Moyers, Bill (PBS) - Hudson River Project, 1998-2007 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - LSR Fund - Moyers, Bill (PBS) - "On Our Own Terms" - Dying in America, 1988-2001 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - LSR Fund - Moyers, Bill (PBS) - Wisdom of Faith, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      With Huston Smith and Genesis Series
    - LSR Fund - Wayfarer Ketch - General, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - LSR Fund - Wayfarer Ketch - Deed of Gift, 1999 May 10 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC), 1948-2009; 1_6
    - LSR - Alternative Medicine, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      The White House Commission on Complementary and Alternative Medicine Policy
    - MSKCC - General, 1997-2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - MSKCC - 620 Park Avenue - Sale, 1988 April 15 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - MSKCC - LSR Nomination - NAS Public Welfare Medal (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - MSKCC - LSR Outpatient Pavilion - General, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - MSKCC - LSR Outpatient Pavilion - Publicity, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - MSKCC - Oral History - LSR Interview, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - MSKCC - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Initiative in Cancer Biology, 2001-2004 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - MSKCC - Lucy's 1987 Presentation (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - MSKCC - The Legacy of Bessie Dashiell, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Photocopy of the original Fred Smith book.
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Mamdouha Bobst, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Nicholas F. Brady, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Hilary Califano, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Anne Cox Chambers, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Albert H. Gordon, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - John W. Kluge, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Carroll Petrie, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - General, 2001-2003 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - LSR pledge, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - LSR Challenge Pledge, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - MSKCC - Capital Campaign - Lucy R. Waletzky, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - MSKCC - General, 1985-2001 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - MSKCC - Resolution for Dr. Paul M. Marks, 1999 December 14 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - MSKCC - Board Meeting, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - MSKCC - Dinner announcing Capital Campaign, 2003 October 23 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - MSKCC - Cassileth, Barrie R., Ph.D. - Integrative Medicine, 1998-2003 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - MSKCC - "MSKCC Celebrates Laurance S. Rockefeller's 50 Years of Service", 1998 February (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - Program - General, 2001-2008 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - Chair in Integrative Medicine - Pledge Letter, 2003 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - Chair in Integrative Medicine - General, 2003-2009 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - LSR Fund - Funding, 2000-2009 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - LSR Fund - 2.5 Million Matching Grant, 2007-2009 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - Operating Results and Budgets, 2001-2009 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - MSKCC - Total, 1975-2006 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - MSKCC - Clinical Problems in Cancer Research Report, 1948-1949 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - American Cancer Society - Fourth Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Memorial Hospital History - Kathy Brennan, 2001 October (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - LSR - MSKCC - Endowed Chairs, 1986 (Box 390, Folder 4)
    - LSR - MSKCC - National Cancer Center, Japan - Partnership for a Single Purpose, 1973 (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Memorials, 1956-2009; 1_7
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Family Service, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Gratuities, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - LSR / MFR Burial, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Meeting Agendas, Task Lists, Logistics, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Printed Materials - Acknowledgment Cards, Invitation, and Program, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Reception, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      General, with Abigail Kirsch Catering contract
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Ushers and Greeters, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - LSR and DR's Condolence Lists, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - LSR's Sympathy Calls and Messages, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Ellen Pomeroy's Condolence Letters, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Condolence Calls received and People contacted, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - General, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Condolence Letters, Telegrams, Condolences, Phone Calls, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Obituary compiled by Associates, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Public Relations, Obituary Notices, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Invitation Lists, 5600, Children's and Family, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Official Photo, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - LSR - Memorial - Book - Woodstock Foundation, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Book and CDs (Distribution List), 2005 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Invitation List, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Program, 2004 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Obituary - New York Times, 2004 July 12 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Obituary - Vermont Standard, 2004 July 15; July 19 2004 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Services - Family - 1960s-1990s (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Services - Friends, 1990s-2000s (Box 107, Folder 7, Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Services - Fair, William R., 2002 January 3 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Services - Schmidt, Benno, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Memorial Services - VanderKemp, Gerald, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      Deceased December 28, 2001
    - Memorial Services - Whyte, Jenny Bell, 2002 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      Deceased September 13, 2002
    - Wedding Service - Davis, Lonna and Robert, 2004 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      Daughter of sculptor, June Harrah. LSR and MFR introduced June Harrah and Jerry Lord (LSR Princeton friend). LSR later arranged for their wedding at the River Club.
    - LSR - Memorial Tribute - MSKCC, 2004 September 27 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Condolences - Condolence Call and Message Logs, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Condolences - Letters, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Condolences - Contributions, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Condolences - Letters to David Rockefeller, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Condolences - Telephone Messages Received, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Memorial - Presentation Items Log - Kent House, 2004 July 16 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Memorial - Funeral Home - LSR Data, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Memorial - Funeral Home - Program, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Memorial - Working Invitation List, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - "People Who Need People", 2004 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Protocol, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Babysitter, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Flowers, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Invitation, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Memos from 5600, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Family Planning Memos, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Caterer and Event Planner, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - John Bowling Associates, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Death Notices, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Obituaries - New York Newspapers, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Press Release, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Out-of-Town Newspapers, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Other, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Obituaries - Tributes, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - Steven C. Rockefeller Reading and Prayer, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Program, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - Naomi Waletzky, Remarks at LSR Memorial Service, 2004 September 9 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - Laura Chasin's Remarks at LSR's Eightieth Birthday, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Hyacinths, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - Isaiah, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - Mary French Rockefeller Chapel Inscription at MSKCC, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - Mother's Bible Quote to LSR, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - St. Francis Prayer, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Readings - 1 Corinthians, 13, 14:1, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Riverside Church - Reverend Forbes, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Riverside Church - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - LSR - Memorials - Jackson Hole, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - MSKCC, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - CD, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Drafts, 1995-2004 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - Singers, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Memorial Service - Music - Hymns, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 3)